Guide to the Annie Dillard Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- May 2000 Acquisition, 1955-2000; 4; 34 boxes
  - Oversize Material
    - Drawings, undated (Box 50)
    - Drawings, undated; 6 (Box 51)
  - Restricted Material
    Boxes 52 and 53 (diaries and notebooks): Restricted. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
    - Diaries and notebooks, 1958-1961; 5 (Box 52)
    - Diaries and notebooks, 1963-1965, undated; 4 (Box 53)
  - Restricted Fragile
    Box 54 (computer disk): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Computer disk from Box 30 (Box 54)
- May 2000 Acquisition, 1999-2000; 5; 0.42; 1 box; )
  Formerly classified as Uncat MSS 64.
  - Untitled typescript photocopy, undated (Box 55)
  - Letter to the editor by Dillard in The Key West Citizen and tear sheets from Academy Awards in Literature award announcement for Dillard, 2000 January 11, undated (Box 55)
  - Connecticut Magazine January 2000 issue with Dillard's contribution to "My Favorite Place" feature, 2000 January (Box 55)
  - Mounted book jacket fragments of Dillard's books, various correspondence with publishers, printed material on Dillard, 1999 (Box 55)
- August 2004 Acquisition, 1991-1992; 6; 0.42; 1 box; )
  Formerly classified as Uncat MSS 695.
  - The Living, drafts, typescript. Includes letter to Kit Reed from Dillard, 1991-1992, undated; 5 (Box 56)
- January 2011 Acquisition, 1960s-2010; 7; 12.17 linear feet (18 boxes)
  This acquisition is orgainzed into the following series: Notebooks, Writings, Correspondence, Personal Papers, Audiovisual Materials, and Restricted Fragile.
  This acquisition consists of notebooks; drafts of many works, including Love and Free Time, and The Maytrees; correspondence, including Gary Clevidence, Blanche Gregory, Rollie McKenna, various friends, and fan mail; personal papers including calendars, clippings, and packing lists; miscellaneous audiovisual materials, and electronic computer files.
  - Notebooks
    - Numbered Notebooks, 1970-2006
      Arranged in the order as numbered by Annie Dillard, equating to a rough chronological order.
      - One - Summer 1970, 1 (Box 57)
      - Two - Sept.-Oct. 1970, 1 (Box 57)
      - Three - Oct.-Dec. 1970 - (visions), 1 (Box 57)
      - Four - Dec. 1970-Feb. 71 - Till Florida, 1970-1971 (Box 57)
      - Five - March-June 1971 incl. Flordia (Box 57)
      - Seven - Eng. Hills Inn - Aug.-Oct. 1971 (Box 57)
      - Eight - Oct. 71-Jan. 72, 1971-1972; 1 (Box 57)
      - Nine - Jan-May 1972, 1 (Box 57)
      - Ten - May-July 1972, 1 (Box 57)
      - Eleven - July-Aug 1972, 1 (Box 57)
      - Twelve - Sept. 1972-Dec., 1 (Box 57)
      - Thirteen - Dec. 72-Feb. 73, 1972-1973; 1 (Box 57)
      - Fourteen - Feb. 73-June 73, 1973; 1 (Box 57)
      - Sixteen - Oct.-Dec. 1973 (Box 57)
      - [Seventeen] - Dec.-Jan. 73-74, 1973-1974; 1 (Box 57)
      - [Eighteen] - Feb-April 1974 (Box 57)
      - Nineteen - April-June 1974, 1 (Box 57)
      - Galapagos - 20. June-Aug., 1974, 1 (Box 57)
      - Aug.-Oct. 1974 - #21, 1 (Box 57)
      - 22 - Oct. 74-Jan. 75 - Crisis in Virginia, 1974-1975 (Box 57)
      - 23 - Jan.-April 1975, 1 (Box 57)
      - 24 - April-Sept. 1975, 1 (Box 57)
      - 25 - Sept. 75-June 76 (Lumme to Waldron), 1975-1976 (Box 57)
      - 26 - June 1976-June 1977, 1976-1977 (Box 58)
      - 27 - June 77-May 78, 1977-1978; 1 (Box 58)
      - 28 - May 17, 1978-April 1979, 1978-1979; 1 (Box 58)
      - 29 - April 1979-July 1980, 1979-1980; 1 (Box 58)
      - 30 - July 1980-June 1981, 1980-1981 (Box 58)
      - [31?] - March 23, 1981-July 5, 1 (Box 58)
      - Fiction Ideas - Aug. 1981-Laschevers-to Spring 82, B'ham, 1981-1982 (Box 58)
      - 33 - 1983 Oct.-Dec., 1 (Box 58)
      - 34 - June 1983-June 1984: Rosie, 1983-1984 (Box 58)
      - 35 - June 84-May 90, 1984-1990; 1 (Box 58)
      - 36 - May 90-91 - Writing the Living - Rosie 6, 1990-1991 (Box 58)
      - #37 - Summer 91 - Cape Walden - Greenland etc., 1991 (Box 58)
      - #38 - Oct. 91-July 92, 1991-1992; 1 (Box 58)
      - 39 - July 92-March 93, 1992-1993; 1 (Box 58)
      - 40 - Summer 93, 1993 (Box 58)
      - 42 - Summer 96 - All the Property Money Can Buy, 1996 (Box 58)
      - 43 - July 94 - Spring 97 - See also small notebook., 1994-1997 (Box 58)
      - 44 - Bob's Surgery - Feb.-Nov. 1977 (Box 58)
      - 45 - Nov. 97-May 98, 1997-1998; 1 (Box 58)
      - 46 - June 98-Jan. 99 - Cape-Mont, ID, Endoc, KW, 1998-1999 (Box 59)
      - 47 - Jan. 99-July 99, 1999; 1 (Box 59)
      - 50 - Dec. 2000-April 2001, 2000-2001 (Box 59)
      - Writing 51 - Maytrees + Summer 2001 (Box 59)
      - 52 - June 02-Feb 03, 2002- 2003; 1 (Box 59)
      - 53 - Oct. 01-June 02, 2001- 2002; 1 (Box 59)
      - 54 - Nov. 03-June 04, 2003-2004; 1 (Box 59)
      - 56 - June 04 to Feb. 05 (Rama Krishne), 2004-2005 (Box 59)
      - 57 - Fall 2004, 1 (Box 59)
        Contains the index for notebook number 59.
      - 58 - 2/05 - 9/05, 2005; 1 (Box 59)
      - 59 - 1/05-7/06, 2005-2006; 1 (Box 59)
    - Other Notebooks, 1970s-2009
      Arranged in rough alphabetical order. Some notebooks from this group may fit into the sequence of numbered notebooks.
      - Untitled, 1970s-1983 (Box 59)
      - Untitled, circa 1988 (Box 59)
      - "A Novel", 1978-1983; 1 (Box 59)
      - American Academy in Rome, circa 1982 (Box 59)
      - AOK Dec. '09, 2009; 1 (Box 59)
      - Asst. Research, Prehistory, circa 1975 (Box 59)
      - China (Box 59)
      - China, 1980s (Box 59)
      - Costa Rica 95 - Tortugas, 1995; 1 (Box 59)
      - "Doe's Guest Cabin writing Holy... through NYC trip", circa 1977 (Box 59)
      - English Musings Notebook, 1 (Box 59)
      - Fairhaven College - teaching notes, circa 1978 (Box 60)
      - Hollins College - Annie Doak, circa 1963-1964 (Box 60)
      - Israel - Spring 94 - von Hugell - Wm. Johnson, 1994 (Box 60)
      - Notes (Box 60)
      - Notebook (Box 60)
      - Notebook, 1980s (Box 60)
      - Notebooks - includes related notes, circa 2005 (Box 60)
      - Sketchbook (Box 60)
      - Sketchbook with one portrait, 1 (Box 60)
      - Small notebooks, two. (Box 60)
      - Temporary Booklist - Spring 06, 2006; 1 (Box 60)
      - Travel notes, circa 1993; 1 (Box 60)
      - Travel notes - Alberta, Canada, 1 (Box 60)
      - Travel notes - Galapagos, 1 (Box 60)
      - Travel notes - Yemen, 1980s; 1 (Box 60)
      - Trip to Canada - 79?, circa 1979; 1 (Box 60)
      - The Verandah - Humboldt - Botsford, circa 1982 (Box 60)
      - "Very Old & Slip but Better'n Nothing", circa 1990s (Box 60)
      - "Working at airport idea: Encounters with Chinese writers - USA division", circa 1984 (Box 60)
  - Writings, 1966-2009
    Arranged in rough alphabetical order.
    - "1st draft of Cape Cod book", 2001 March 16; 1 (Box 60)
    - "1st draft or early draft of Cape Cod book", 2001 March 16; 1 (Box 60)
    - "40s" - research clippings, circa 1992; 1 (Box 60)
    - Alone - drafts and notes, 2003-2004; 1 (Box 60)
    - An American Childhood, outtakes, 1 (Box 60)
    - "Archive, dec - From Key-West desktop", 1 (Box 60)
    - "Archive - uncollected, some worthwhile to scholars", 2000s; 2 (Box 60)
      Contains uncollected prose, nonfiction and journalism that Annie Dillard considered not worth publishing.
    - Articles and notes, 1980s-1980s; 1 (Box 60)
    - Book lists, 1966; 1997; 1 (Box 60)
    - "Books 95-02", 1995 March 24-2002 November; 1 (Box 61)
    - Camping Ft. Jeff, 1 (Box 61)
    - Castine - chapter, 1 (Box 61)
    - Commencement address, 1978; 1 (Box 61)
    - A Conversation of Southerners, 2005; 1 (Box 61)
      Related Archival Materials note
      See also: Audiovisual Materials, Box 73.
    - Daddy's Funeral, 1 (Box 61)
    - "Dead Book - Don't Publish", 2009 July 1; 1 (Box 61)
    - Defects 2, 1998; 1 (Box 61)
      Contains the discarded long version sent to Harper's, circa February 1998.
    - Drafts, 2005 December 22; 2 (Box 61)
      Copies of electronic files are available through Access Services: Disks #3 and #4.
    - Drafts and published articles, 1 (Box 61)
    - Drafts, notes, and related clippings, 2000s; 1 (Box 61)
    - Draft on trails in CT, 1 (Box 61)
    - Drafts, clippings & miscellaneous material, 2005-2007; 1 (Box 61)
    - Epigraphs, etc., 2002; 1 (Box 61)
    - For the Time Being - notes, 2007 April. 20; 1 (Box 61)
    - Holy the Firm - varioius drafts and articles, 1977; 1 (Box 61)
    - Index cards, 4 (Box 61)
    - Indexes, circa 1970; 1 (Box 61)
    - "Journal 1967", 1967 April 27-November 30; 1 (Box 61)
    - KW - Annie - Grinnell - St. Study, circa 2003; 1 (Box 61)
    - "Lacks epilogue, almost done" - draft, 2006 February; 1 (Box 61)
    - Leaving - notes and drafts, 2002 June 6; 1 (Box 61)
    - "Leaving - Formerly Beg" - notes and drafts, 2002 February 15; 1 (Box 61)
    - Love and Free Time, 1 (Box 61)
    - Love and Free Time - old version - late Feb. 06, 2006; 1 (Box 61)
    - "M dying (again)", 1 (Box 61)
    - The Maytrees
      - "One" - notes and drafts, 2002 February 15; 1 (Box 61)
      - "Two" - notes and drafts, 2002 February 15; 1 (Box 61)
      - "Three - her fantasies" - notes and drafts, 2002 February 16 (Box 61)
      - The Maytrees - "1st Pass (terrible)", 2006 November 16; 1 (Box 61)
      - The Maytrees - "2nd Pass", 2007 January 26; 2 (Box 61)
      - The Maytrees - "2nd Pass", 2007 January 26; 2 (Box 62)
      - The Maytrees Archive - Alone, 2004 February 10; 1 (Box 62)
      - The Maytrees Archive - " Alone with Castine H" (Box 62)
      - The Maytrees Archive - drafts and letter, 2003 December 31 (Box 62)
      - The Maytrees Archive - Epilogue, 2005 June 28; 1 (Box 62)
      - The Maytrees - bound proof, 2007; 1 (Box 62)
      - The Maytrees - dead drafts, 2001 June-2002 October; 3 (Box 62)
      - The Maytrees - drafts, 2005-2006; 12 (Box 62)
      - The Maytrees, "HBRO Archive" - ending, 1998 June (Box 62)
      - The Maytrees, "HBRO Archive" - notes and clippings, circa 2005 (Box 62)
      - The Maytrees, "HBRO Archive" - notes and drafts (Box 62)
      - The Maytrees, "HBRO Archive" - unrevised draft, 2 (Box 63)
      - The Maytrees - "inexplicable segment from.. .", draft, 2006 November (Box 63)
      - The Maytrees - "lacks epilogue, almost done", 2006 February (Box 63)
      - The Maytrees - notes, 1998-2001; 5 (Box 63)
      - The Maytrees - notes and drafts (Box 63)
      - The Maytrees - notes, drafts and papers, circa 2000 (Box 63)
    - The Maytrees, "Transfiguration," "Lenses" - notes, drafts, and a photograph, 1 (Box 63)
    - Middle America's Puritans, 1987 October; 1 (Box 63)
    - "More shack list 35 - brain!", 2002 June- 2003 February; 1 (Box 63)
    - Nonfiction as Art, 1983 April; 1 (Box 63)
    - Notes, 2005 -2006; 6 (Box 63)
    - Notes and drafts, 2001-2007; 12 (Box 63)
    - Notes and miscellaneous, circa 1997; 1 (Box 64)
    - Notes, drafts, and other papers, 1 (Box 64)
    - Notes, drafts, and travel invoice, circa 2002; 1 (Box 64)
    - "Part of Verse?" - notes, 1 (Box 64)
    - Pilgrim - drafts, 1 (Box 64)
    - Poetry, 1 (Box 64)
    - "Primer Biblio", 1968-1985; 1 (Box 64)
    - Solares Hill, 2004 January 9; 2 (Box 69 Oversize)
    - "Stars" - notes and drafts, 2002 January 4; 1 (Box 64)
    - "Stars archive" - notes, 2003 January 20; 1 (Box 64)
    - "Summer 2001 - Monastery - Reading John S. Donne, The Way of All the World" - "Lune Shacks twice, working on Cape novel, Sandhi, Buddha, etc., 2 (Box 64)
    - "These are dead drafts from Summer 02", 2002; 1 (Box 64)
    - "This = nonfiction", 1 (Box 64)
    - Title / author list, 1968-1980s; 3 (Box 64)
    - Transfiguration - photocopies from Norton Reade r, 1986; 1 (Box 64)
    - Typed notes, 1 (Box 64)
    - "Uncollected & unpublished", 1970s-2000s; 3 (Box 64)
    - "Unedited (mostly) fiction", circa 1983; 1 (Box 64)
    - "Unused finished stuff", 1 (Box 64)
    - Various drafts, 1980s-2001; 3 (Box 64)
    - Various drafts, and articles, 1980s-1990s; 1 (Box 65)
    - Various material, 1 (Box 65)
    - Various writings and notes, circa 1992; 1 (Box 65)
    - Walden Pond and Thoreau - Master's Thesis, 1968 and Related Papers, 1970s, 1968-1970s; 1 (Box 65)
    - The Wreck of Time - Harper's, 1998 January; 1 (Box 65)
  - Correspondence, 1979-2009
    Arranged in rough chronological order.
    - Clevidence, Gary, 1979; 2 (Box 66)
      Contains laminated originals, as well as preservation photocopies.
    - Grades, recommendations, evaluations and notes, 1980s; 3 (Box 66)
    - Gregory, Blanche, 1982-1984; 1 (Box 66)
    - McKenna, Rollie, 1992-1993; 1 (Box 66)
    - 1997-2005, 1 (Box 66)
    - 1997-2005, 1 (Box 66)
      Includes clippings, notes, and various drafts.
    - Fan mail to Cape Cod, 1998-2002; 1 (Box 66)
    - Lit Business, 1998-2005; 2 (Box 66)
    - Friends, 1999-2001; 1 (Box 66)
    - Friends, 2000-2002; 2 (Box 66)
    - 2000-2005, 3 (Box 66)
    - 2001-2002, 2 (Box 66)
    - 2001-2002, 1 (Box 67)
    - Religious colleges and institutions, 2001-2002; 1 (Box 67)
    - 2002-2003, 1 (Box 67)
    - 2003-2006, 1 (Box 67)
    - Friends, 2003-2006; 2 (Box 67)
    - Offers, 2004-2006; 1 (Box 67)
    - 2005-2006, 1 (Box 67)
      Includes notes and other papers.
    - circa 2006, 1 (Box 67)
    - 2007-2009, 1 (Box 67)
      Includes artwork and other papers.
    - circa 2008, 1 (Box 67)
    - circa 2008, 1 (Box 67)
      Includes Japanese cover images.
    - circa 2009, 1 (Box 67)
  - Personal Papers, 1964-2010
    - Cargoes - photocopies, 1964-1966; 1 (Box 67)
    - Correspondence, clippings, notes, articles, and other papers, 1980s-2000s; 2 (Box 67)
    - Article regarding Annie Dillard, 1987; 1 (Box 67)
    - Calendars and notes, 1988-1990; 1 (Box 69 Oversize)
    - Calendars and notes, 1991-2002; 4 (Box 70 Oversize)
    - Inklings, 1997; 1 (Box 69 Oversize)
    - Papers regarding Annie Dillard bio article, 1998-2002; 2 (Box 67)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 2000-2003; 1 (Box 67)
    - Clippings and notes, circa 2001; 1 (Box 67)
    - Packing Lists, 2001; 1 (Box 67)
    - Notes, clippings, correspondence, and other papers, 2001-2002; 1 (Box 67)
    - Correspondence, clippings and other papers, 2001-2005; 1 (Box 67)
    - Harper's Magazine, 2002 June; 1 (Box 67)
    - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges Award, Lifetime Achievement Award - certificate, 2002; 1 (Box 67)
    - Virginia Foundation for Independent Colleges Award - glass framed, 2002; 1 (Box 72 Oversize)
      Contains plaque from the 50th Anniversary of the Virgina Foundation for Independent Colleges Award, 12 July 2002.
    - Provincetown Pocket Book, 2002-2003; 1 (Box 67)
    - Clippings and Harper's Magazine, 2003-2006; 1 (Box 67)
    - Calendars, 2003-2010; 3 (Box 71 Oversize)
    - Miscellaneous papers, circa 2004; 1 (Box 67)
    - Articles and clippings, 2004-2008; 1 (Box 67)
      Copies of electronic files are available through Access Services: Disks #5
    - Articles and clippings, 2004-2008; 1 (Box 68)
    - Reviews - The Maytrees, circa 2007; 1 (Box 68)
    - Phone numbers, 1 (Box 68)
    - "I Slept Out" - child's workbook, 1 (Box 68)
  - Audiovisual Materials, 2005
    Box 73 (audiovisual material): Restricted fragile material. Reference copy may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - A Conversation of Southerners, Side A/B (1 of 3 audiocassettes), 2005; 1 (Box 73, Item barcode 39002109970138)
    - A Conversation of Southerners, Side C/D (2 of 3 audiocassettes), 2005; 1 (Box 73, Item barcode 39002109970146)
    - A Conversation of Southerners, Side E/F (3 of 3 audiocassettes), 2005; 1 (Box 73, Item barcode 39002109970153)
    - Transfiguration, by Stephen Andrew Taylor and The Weasel Song by John Zainea - audio compact discs, circa 2004 (Box 73)
      Copies of electronic files are available through Access Services: Disks #1 and #2.
    - "James Harley - Wild Fruits: Prologue 16:10" (Box 73)
      Copies of electronic files are available through Access Services: Disk #45.
  - Computer Media, 2000s
    - Stephen Andrew Taylor Transfiguration (21:54) text from Annie Dillard's Holy the Firm Quad City Symphony Orchestra, Donald Schleicher dir. Mary Wilson, soprano; Emily Lodine, mezzo-sop; Eric Ashcraft, tenor; Paul Grizzell, bass premiere, 10/2/2004, 2011-ycal-41606-0001; 1 (Box 74)
    - the weasel song by john zainea, inspired by annie dillard's essay "living like weasels", 2011-ycal-41606-0002; 1 (Box 74)
    - 3.15.4 two new, 2011-ycal-41606-0003; 1 (Box 74)
    - dos word all early Aug 05 before Dc/7, 2011-ycal-41606-0004; 1 (Box 74)
    - Alone leaving 8.19.5 3, 2011-ycal-41606-0005; 1 (Box 74)
    - FAST SPEED DIAL UP VA W[illegible] load on Dc/1 w/Cx Cr 56c modem V, 2011-ycal-41606-0006; 1 (Box 74)
    - Norton 2004 Internet Security, 2011-ycal-41606-0007; 1 (Box 74)
    - 2005 5.18 I hope 19 3.22-5 2.15.5 alone Wed Annie 5/27/5 epilogue archive - "Moving.doc" disk failed, 2011-ycal-41606-0008; 1 (Box 74)
    - I rosie forget a aging vita 6/6/99 7/24/99 3/15/00 l;a two OK 12/1 4/19 4/26/00 5/10/00 a.doc for KFZ has.prd files/l2 Nov 25, 00 27 has old "L" right before I separated it, 2011-ycal-41606-0009; 1 (Box 74)
    - [no label information], 2011-ycal-41606-0010; 1 (Box 74)
    - [no label information], 2011-ycal-41606-0011; 1 (Box 74)
    - 2/26/06 BACKUP FLASH DRIVE --BEG 75 BOOK --, 2011-ycal-41606-0012; 1 (Box 74)
    - [no label information], 2011-ycal-41606-0013; 1 (Box 74)
    - [no label information], 2011-ycal-41606-0014; 1 (Box 74)
    - [no label information], 2011-ycal-41606-0015; 1 (Box 74)
    - [no label information], 2011-ycal-41606-0016; 1 (Box 74)
    - [no label information], 2011-ycal-41606-0017; 1 (Box 74)
    - One 1.18.6 beg75 archive frozen, 2011-ycal-41606-0018; 1 (Box 74)
    - 12.7 abiblio / 12.11 alone / sky / frozen 1/12/4 coll 1/17/4, 2011-ycal-41606-0019; 1 (Box 74)
    - Aug 6 05 WINWORD alone 1 one Bret Paint epilogue or preface or paraphernalia stars epilogue 8/27/5, 2011-ycal-41606-0020; 1 (Box 74)
    - 9/3 oct 1 10/3 all 7/23 1 two 5/9 all of it all of this 02 5/14 last S'/Oal 8/13 all of Jr; in chaps! incl extras, 2011-ycal-41606-0021; 1 (Box 74)
    - Amy + Molly 7/19/5 shack alone "?too old? scez formatted Living 9/26/5, 2011-ycal-41606-0022; 1 (Box 74)
    - epilogue preface Keep 2 beg75 stars 2 names painting European verse archive, 2011-ycal-41606-0023; 1 (Box 74)
    - 10/02 vita Aug 3/5 saved fairly decent files alone 4 learning 8/8 in Win word learning alone beg75, 2011-ycal-41606-0024; 1 (Box 74)
    - 12/5 preface words sky 3/8/01 names 5/26 6/12 DRAFT 10/13 beg one two three four five l end archive frozen verse names, 2011-ycal-41606-0025; 1 (Box 74)
    - 8.13.5 alone 3 9.16 shack alone, 2011-ycal-41606-0026; 1 (Box 74)
    - 2/17/5 3/20 4/3 Moving letter.doc A 28 2/28/5/25 alone.doc in correct format but few corrections OH LORDY, 2011-ycal-41606-0027; 1 (Box 74)
    - 9/25 courtship again preface 1 shack, 2011-ycal-41606-0028; 1 (Box 74)
    - 7.2 Fri 8/13? 1; two; twonew; twotwo; thru; starry; alone; leaving, castine1, castine2, scene, shack, sky, end, epilogue, epigraph, pusend, end words, love, names, vorse, sky, preface3, preface, frozen, jan20 April 23, 04 MAYTREE BOOK 7.8.5 8.3.5, 2011-ycal-41606-0029; 1 (Box 74)
    - newly formatted 4/15/3 IBM 4/15/02 ALLOFIT2.doc; a.doc; old a.doc, 2011-ycal-41606-0030; 1 (Box 74)
    - 4/15/03 33yorker.doc; AGING.doc; ALONE.doc; booklist.doc; CASTINE2.doc; CHK.doc; COURTING.doc; END.doc; FRAGEN.doc; FRISCH.doc; HOUSESIT.doc; LEAVING.doc; NAMES.doc; OLDA.doc; ONE.doc; PREFACE.doc; PREFACE2.txt; PREFACE3.doc; PUBEND.doc; SCENE.doc; SHACK.doc; SKY.doc; STARS.doc; STARS1.doc; two.doc; TWOPUB.doc; twotwo.doc; WORDS.doc (more...) ...BIBLIO.doc; CASTINE1.doc, 2011-ycal-41606-0031; 1 (Box 74)
    - alonemess.doc doc4.doc is a bitch: alone dating back to early Aug, no corrections, BUT AT LEAST it isn't in lil tiny pages! it is alone, 2011-ycal-41606-0032; 1 (Box 74)
    - 8/4/5 = ALL DOS 05.doc, 2011-ycal-41606-0033; 1 (Box 74)
    - 2000/10-8 Oct 12, 2000 6/13/01 castine 7/15/01 archive, 2011-ycal-41606-0034; 1 (Box 74)
    - 4/15/03: 1.txt; allofit.doc; archive.doc; address book changes original.doc; castine1.doc; castine2.doc; DOSAARCH.doc; newaddresses.doc; I.doc; YORKER.doc, 2011-ycal-41606-0035; 1 (Box 74)
    - both books July 10, 04 8/4 epilogue 8/26/4 some in win format: alone one epilogue two twotwo, 2011-ycal-41606-0036; 1 (Box 74)
    - 9/18/4 winword 1 twotwo ALLOFIT2 1/24 ready to leave KW 4/24/4-two epilogue 8/26/4 Dem Pico 6/18/4 alone scene leaving end2 <-- August 26, 04, 2011-ycal-41606-0037; 1 (Box 74)
    - 8/4/5 book to put in new external floppy word dos, 2011-ycal-41606-0038; 1 (Box 74)
    - 8/12/5 alone, beg75, windows duplicate but all alone 8/3 8.20 alone beg75 leaving, 2011-ycal-41606-0039; 1 (Box 74)
    - Dillard Maytrees files early 2000s, 2011-ycal-41606-0040; 1 (Box 74)
    - DILLARD 7-7571 11/17 WE DOING (IN NUMBERS) Book Book Nov 15, 97 before Jelle MICROSOFT WORD 6.0 FOR DOS NOT FOR WINDOWS old BOOK.DOC, 2011-ycal-41606-0041; 1 (Box 74)
    - all the novel from dos word 11/30/03 doth copy ? needs allofit, 2011-ycal-41606-0042; 1 (Box 74)
    - allofit2 (dosword) 11/30/3 timeline chk archive2 words/biblio vorse supplements lav disk with actual chaps, 2011-ycal-41606-0043; 1 (Box 74)
    - ANNIE DILLARD ART, 2011-ycal-41606-0044; 1 (Box 74)
    - JAMES HARLEY WILD FRUITS: PROLOGUE 16:10, 2011-ycal-41606-0045; 1 (Box 74)
    - DOS disk abiblio arandom etrusion fngel ahowforum amath ahowlost alengs arefound, 2011-ycal-41606-0046; 1 (Box 74)
    - pico.doc (for Gregg), 2011-ycal-41606-0047; 1 (Box 74)
    - 2000 108 (as of Wed 10/11/2008 (+a + vorse) 11/27 CEDU.doc 6/26/4 alone 2/22/5 lr d2 in wi style whole, 2011-ycal-41606-0048; 1 (Box 74)
    - 1 one two beg75 shackalone (best version of alon) 59?, 2011-ycal-41606-0049; 1 (Box 74)
    - 9/21/5 shackalone, 2011-ycal-41606-0050; 1 (Box 74)
    - early Maytrees (rorsc.doc is historical + atmospherical stuff), 2011-ycal-41606-0051; 1 (Box 74)
    - Cape 4/25 + Murder allofit.doc a.doc 5/14/02 sky, 2011-ycal-41606-0052; 1 (Box 74)
    - 2/2/5 33yorker archive frozen stars leaving vorse Alone won't download, 2011-ycal-41606-0053; 1 (Box 74)
    - HIT ME 1/4, 2011-ycal-41606-0054; 1 (Box 74)
    - 12.3.3 estruscan, 2011-ycal-41606-0055; 1 (Box 74)
    - odds + ends preface (34,xxx) frisch sky fragen words biblio vorse, 2011-ycal-41606-0056; 1 (Box 74)
    - leaving shackalone scene preface 9/26, 2011-ycal-41606-0057; 1 (Box 74)
    - epilogue end stars courtship (also on computer as courtship 9 9/26/5, 2011-ycal-41606-0058; 1 (Box 74)
    - a.doc (addresses), 2011-ycal-41606-0059; 1 (Box 74)
    - 2/14/02 2/15, 2011-ycal-41606-0060; 1 (Box 74)
    - [no label information], 2011-ycal-41606-0061; 1 (Box 74)
    - almost done! 3-23add.doc oddaddresses (<-- formerly archive) (ignore others) completed oldaddresses (formerly named archive) addressb.changes orig. LATEST, 2011-ycal-41606-0062; 1 (Box 74)
    - Nov 03 29 files copied from C onto a - down to twopub.doc 12/4/3 forever friday, 2011-ycal-41606-0063; 1 (Box 74)
    - 2/4/5, 2011-ycal-41606-0064; 1 (Box 74)
    - beg75 1/30/6, 2011-ycal-41606-0065; 1 (Box 74)
    - 11/18/01, 2011-ycal-41606-0066; 1 (Box 74)
    - Book 2/15/02 preface one two three stars leaving alone, castine1, castine2, scene, [end], vorse, names, words, fragen, epilogue, 2011-ycal-41606-0067; 1 (Box 74)
    - 11.22.4 alone preface preface leaving scene end epilogue pubend shaik sky words fragen archive archive2 twotwo stars louisa dunno cloves aging 1.18.05 alone fragen acorns 1/22 alone archive, 2011-ycal-41606-0068; 1 (Box 74)
    - 3/1/6 beg75 Annie Dillard, 2011-ycal-41606-0069; 1 (Box 74)
    - [no label information], 2011-ycal-41606-0070; 1 (Box 74)
    - [no label information], 2011-ycal-41606-0071; 1 (Box 74)